Sorry, follow!
I'm really amazed that you set a ball from that low.
You could just go underhanded.
Oh, no, I couldn't, because it is my job to set.
I'm responsible for getting the ball to the best spot.
So?
So, underhand, I only have my two arms.
Overhand, I've got ten fingers.
I want the most contact points to get better support.
Because I'm a setter!
I'm on a team with someone who plays volleyball like that.
I've been half-assing everything so much.
Rusecki, we don't need you to just get the ball over the net.
I was almost certain I'd never get another chance.
Even the best team in the world can't keep doing exactly the same things, or they'll find
themselves knocked off their top spot.
Huh?
And we aren't even the best team in Japan.
Not yet.
If yesterday satisfies us, what happens tomorrow?
Opportunities are out there, son.
You have to challenge yourself today.
We'll be right back.
Nice serve!
Opportunities are out there, son.
You have to challenge yourself today.
Nice serve, Riseki!
In a complete 180 from the second set, Riseki lets loose a tremendous serve!
Yes! Yes!
Yes!
That's what I'm talking about!
This guy's manageable, let's shut him down right now.
Yes, sir!
So basically every person in Inarizaki's cheer squad is like that old guy with the mutton chops.
If they think a play is good, they cheer.
If not, they boo.
After a quick timeout, it's Riseki's turn to serve again.
Can he keep his concentration?
Tanaka!
It's long!
Threw them off with a serve and then Alan Ojiro nails it!
All right!
That was masterfully done!
Nice!
Nice kill, Alan!
Jump, jump, Alan!
And just like that, Inarizaki has caught up to Karasuno!
Don't panic, you guys!
We're fine.
Hey, nice job, dude.
I'll get three points next time.
You gotta dream bigger than three points.
Ten at least.
One hundred percent.
Gene!
He's really coming for him now.
Nice serve!
Kageyama!
Left!
Tanaka!
Number five on the left has a brutal cut shot.
But...
It's just a cheap imitation.
You're nothing but a bad copy of Bokuto.
And it's blocked!
Tanaka's been on a roll ever since the end of the first set.
But now they've stopped him in his tracks.
Looks like third-year-o Mimi has finally filled up the hole in Inarizaki's defense.
Inarizaki didn't only find a way to catch up.
With that run, they managed to turn things around and take the lead.
With 13 points, Inarizaki is well on their way to getting this game under control.
Now at the midway point, the teams will change sides.
It would seem that the serves from first-year Rizeki have turbocharged Inarizaki.
They're really picking up steam now.
Aggressive serves are a powerful standalone weapon.
They can put pressure on the opposition while simultaneously galvanizing the server's own team.
Of course, it's not as easy as it looks.
Will Karasuno be able to stop Inarizaki's momentum?
Inarizaki is still showing some instability.
Each team member is a skilled player, but they don't always work well together.
And their aggression can sometimes backfire on them.
But the opposite is also true.
And that's why they call them the ultimate challengers.
The fact that they ranked second in the country is proof of that.
It's gonna get rough if they don't end the streak right here and now.
Who the hell cares about being second in Japan?
Second?
Or third?
And it doesn't really matter.
That was yesterday.
Cover!
Yesterday is already digested.
Finish it, Kageyama!
Lots of yesterdays have already been converted into muscle.
That was a difficult shot, but Kageyama got it back over and right at center of Tsumumiya!
Asamu!
But Inarizaki still has...
Osamumiya!
The number two over the center.
Or the ace on the left side.
What are we gonna do today?
Twin quick minus tempo!
Reverse!
What just happened?
Nice kill at Tsumumu!
Drop, drop at Tsumumu!
Whoa!
Unbelievable!
The spiker sets the ball to the center!
And together they deliver a stunning minus tempo quick attack!
The Mia twins are a force to be reckoned with, Bill!
If yesterday satisfies us, what happens tomorrow?
What the hell?
Damn!
Yeah!
But just so you know, it was too low on a bit short.
You just can't be choosers, you ungrateful jerk!
I'm not a true center!
But if we tried, I bet we could land a Skylove hurricane now!
Sure, fun!
You're on bottom!
What?
We both know you're on bottom!
That was a fluke!
Don't let it get to you!
Nope!
Right!
Even if it was a fluke, it's still bound to shake the other team's confidence some.
Bet you're right.
That must feel awful.
First, we take the lead away.
Then we hit you with a move you didn't see coming.
Anyone will be panicking.
I bet you want to get out of this funk.
At times like this, pulling off a spectacular kill would clear the air instantly and improve
your team's morale.
You want to get that spike over even if it kills you.
But even if it kills us...
We'll stop it.
And he's shut down!
Inanazaki has stopped Karasuno's ace, Azumari Asahi!
I think that if this keeps up...
Karasuno is going to lose.
I hit the last one way too hard!
I'm sorry!
Probably because you're...
Guess he touched the net.
Shut the trap!
That's lucky.
But the mental beating that's happening is still far worse for Karasuno.
Now we can catch up.
Dammit.
I've been managing to block out Inanazaki's cheer squad, but it feels like they're closing
in again.
Get out there, Hinata!
And now Karasuno's bringing middle blocker Hinata up to the front.
This kid is not only an excellent scorer, but one of the best decoys we'll see in this
tournament.
Karasuno's trying to tie this thing up.
Please, Hinata.
I'm backing you.
You gotta do something.
Asahi!
It's up!
Hinata!
And Inanazaki lost control of the ball, but...
Ojiro fires off a powerful smash!
Hinata!
It seems to me Inanazaki's blocks are just getting more and more accurate.
Kageyama.
Hmm?
It hurts to ask you to do this, but...
Hinata!
Yes!
Nice kill!
And now Kageyama's up to serve.
Go for it, Kageyama!
Karasuno is really going to need those breakpoints.
Number nine has a powerful serve.
And they've got three attackers up front, including number ten.
That's their most dangerous rotation.
Chance ball!
Oh!
Ugh, I hate this rotation.
You're not getting breakpoint!
Nice receive!
Crap, it's long!
I'm done.
I'm gonna stop him!
Yes!
Hang on!
What's the other team getting that point for?
It was a reachover.
Huh?
Hinata and Tanaka probably thought they were blocking Asumu's dump.
But instead, he was actually about to do a set.
Ultimately, it's against the rules to touch the ball when it's still in the other team's court.
Son of a bitch.
You baited him into doing that.
We both know that the one who dominates the net isn't the big tall guy or the middle blockers.
It's the one whose turf is the net.
The setter.
And now the rotation brings back Hinata Zaki's most powerful server, Asumu Miya.
We'll see if Karasuno can survive another Asumu onslaught.
Whoa!
That ball went directly back into Hinata Zaki's court!
Karasuno does survive a bit longer, Phil.
Seems like Karasuno is just barely hanging on down there.
Yeah.
Tsukishima?
Kick some ass out there!
Dammit.
Now there's setters in the back, so they're all in position to use the twins quick again.
Block them, guys.
Please!
That receive goes back to the center.
Who will Asumu Miya use?
The attack comes from the left with Hitoshi Kijima!
Hell yeah!
But Karasuno's premier blocker Tsukishima stands in his way!
One more time!
Man, I got it!
Usamu!
Huh?
Asumu Miya once again turns first contact directly into a set!
You're not Tsukishima.
Tsukishima is on point today.
Osamu Miya is waiting to slam it down!
What?
The ball is set to Asumu Miya, and he sets it right back!
Karasuno's blockers are totally left in the cold!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Dammit.
And coming from behind, it's Alan Ojudo!
Oh!
Ugh!
Ah!
Impressive.
After a long stretch of time that likely had seen more than its share of adversity.
Very rarely do you see something like this.
A play that gets your heart racing just thinking about it.
A play that revives your lost confidence.
After a long, strenuous climb to the top, it serves as the foothold you so desperately need.
It's not a miracle.
It may be one play out of a hundred, or even out of a thousand.
But it's something you went and took for yourself.
When you take hold and connect these rare moments, they allow you to climb higher and higher.
I never thought the day would come when I'd say this to you, but...
Nice receive.
They'll see you from the top.
But hey, you don't have to be in such a hurry.
Meanwhile, don't underestimate your new job.
Without the play of your personal setter, Kageyama, I don't see you as being worth anything.
He who climbs the ladder must start out at the bottom.
What are you trying to accomplish?
Set, it's a bit low.
He's struggling with his approach.
A blocker straight ahead of him.
Even without their Yubaro, Kareseo kills that intense attack perfectly.
Courtesy of middle blocker Shouyo Hidata.
The kid's a real treat to watch.
A nice receiver.
Is that a fluke?
I mean, I guess you could call it that.
But they can't always be just luck, even if they are flukes.
Hmm.
I don't know what to call it.
But there was definitely a concentrated intent behind his actions.
The instant he made contact with the ball, he absorbed its force, using his whole body to kill its speed.
That slow spin.
It's perfect.
No, I'm not going to say it.
I'm not saying it yet.
Counter!
Let's go!
Breakpoint time!
Synchronized attack!
Everyone!
It's just one point, but it's one we cannot let them have.
The mood of the game has changed, and I don't like it.
Stop them!
Follow!
Three blockers!
Great job, guys!
Nice wipe!
What the damn he's fast?
It's still in the air!
Can Anazaki send it back?
Yes!
Breakback!
One more time!
You've got to be kidding me.
No!
It wasn't a breakpoint.
It didn't even get us to matchpoint.
But even so, that single point was more than enough to shatter their spirits.
And once their spirits are broken, their bodies suddenly remember all the exhaustion that's
been building up.
Now, Specs.
That really showed phenomenal persistence on both sides.
But does Anazaki still draw the smile of the goddess of victory?
Anazaki scraped by there, and Karasano put it all into those two attacks.
It must have hurt to get stopped.
That was so close.
Yeah.
I don't want to lose.
I won't let them beat us.
I'm not going to let this end.
We're not gonna...
Did you see that?
Did you see my receive just now?
Missed it.
You're a liar!
I heard you say nice receive!
I heard you!
That's okay.
Just make sure and watch me get the next one!
It's so hard sometimes.
That you just want to stop.
But you can't.
You have to get over it.
We're only at the first step.
It's like he's having a good meal.
Huh?
Okay, seriously.
What is it about this match that's making you think so much about food?
You know how you eat too much yakiniku or whatever and make yourself sick?
So you figure you've had enough to last your whole life.
Then you want some the very next day?
No, if I've just had yakiniku, I'd rather have curry or sushi.
Each of us eats several times every day.
Then we get hungry again.
And it always makes us happy whenever we get food.
It happens again and again.
But it still makes us just as happy every single time.
Oh yeah.
You do always look happy to be alive when you're eaten.
No matter what's in front of you.
Even if you're having cold rice balls or soggy ramen.
That's how it is.
For that guy.
Hmm.
He plays volleyball.
Like he'd starve without it.
I mean, you know.
If you have a bite of something and you're starving.
It makes you even hungrier.
Yeah, I get what you're saying.
When they see someone enjoying their food that much.
Everyone else gets hungry too.
確かなことはいつか
分かる時が来るから
間違ったっていいさ
今思いを止めないで
バカマダムが
ゼルト
Stan
ラー
イチュラー
エチュラー
スクービス
目
パコ
Thank you.